rinkworks.com 2016-11-06

# RinkWorks: Privacy Policy

_RinkWorks_ respects the privacy and confidentially of its associates and readers. Below is our policy regarding the privacy of Internet users. 

  * _RinkWorks_ does not acquire or collect any personal information about you for any reasons other than internal use, except where explicitly indicated. Any and all personal information collected for internal use will be treated confidentially; it will not be given out, nor will it be used for any purpose other than the operation of the RinkWorks site. (For example, some of our online features require registration to participate. If there is a technical problem, or a question we have concerning your use of the feature, we will use your email address, as submitted to us upon registration, to contact you about these matters. Your email address will not, however, be sold or given out to anyone.) RinkWorks does, however, accrue anonymous information which is specific to its readers' browsing habits on RinkWorks. This information is anonymous; it does not contain personal details, although it does contain non-personally identifying details, including, but not limited to, your IP address and the browser you are using. This information is obtained solely for the purpose of tracking traffic flow patterns through the RinkWorks site and measuring levels of interest and accessibility in different areas of RinkWorks.

    * An addendum to the above, RinkWorks does, in some explicitly documented instances, collect voluntarily-supplied personal information, including but not limited to the Demographic Survey, which is used to collect information about the types of visitors RinkWorks receives, is voluntary, and is always anonymous. In this and all other cases where RinkWorks asks for personal information, it will be kept strictly confidential and used only for the purposes expressed when it is asked for.

  * RinkWorks uses third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our web site. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp). 

These companies may also temporarily store some code within your browser that allows the advertising agencies we work with to respond properly to the ads that are delivered. These codes are commonly known as "cookies." The cookies served in conjunction with the advertising are not the doing, nor the responsibility of RinkWorks.

For more information please see the following details associated with a subset of the advertising agencies we work with:

    * _From BURST! Media's privacy policy:_ "When you are first served a BURST! ad, BURST! may temporarily store some codes within your browser that allows us to respond properly to the ads that we deliver. These codes are commonly known as "cookies." For example, these codes let us keep track of how many times you view an ad we distribute. It also helps us determine where to send you when you click on an ad. Unlike many other ad networks, we do not use cookies for the purpose of setting unique identifiers that are used to identify you whenever you return to a web site within the BURST! network. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually change your browser to prevent that use if you desire." 

    * _Concerning ValueClick/Fastclick:_ "We have contracted with ValueClick to monitor certain pages of our web site for the purpose of reporting website traffic, statistics, advertisement 'click-throughs,' and/or other activities on our web site. Where authorized by us, ValueClick may use cookies, web beacons, and/or other monitoring technologies to compile anonymous statistics about our website visitors. No personally identifiable information is collected by or transferred to any party other than the Advertiser. For more information about how the information is collected and used by ValueClick, please see ValueClick's privacy policy at <http://media.valueclick.com/privacy_consumer.shtml>. 

  * This web site contains links to other sites. This privacy policy is for the sole use and purpose of RinkWorks and does not cover the sites RinkWorks links to. Please be aware that RinkWorks is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage you to read the privacy practices of each and every web site that collects your personal information. 

  * This site makes public forums available to you, including, but not limited to, the Message Forum and RinkChat. Please be aware, whenever you post personal information online, through the Message Forum, RinkChat, or other public online area, that this information can be collected and used by others. RinkWorks assumes any and all information posted to these public areas as intended for public disclosure. 

  * RinkWorks takes reasonable security measures to protect the loss, inappropriate disclosure, and misuse of the information under our control. However, should a breach in security occur and information stolen or altered by anyone, RinkWorks cannot be held responsible for this loss or theft.
